[music]
[Instructor] All right. So let's
get started with Prototype 3.
Now I'm going to import
the Project files,
and set up my new Unity Project.
But since we've already done
that let me just open up Unity
so that we can get going.
Now I'm going to go
into the scenes Folder,
underneath my Project window.
Open up "Prototype 3",
by double-clicking on it.
I'm going to delete my sample scene
by right-clicking on it.
Delete. Let me reposition
my Camera here.
I'm on the other side, okay. Cool.
So that looks like what's
in our Game View,
and then last but not least,
once I've had all my Assets imported
you can actually select
the Background Object
in the scene on the right side,
you'll see in the Inspector
for the Background,
this "Sprite Renderer".
Now a Sprite Renderer is a Component
that enables you to render
or to see images in your game,
and in your environment.
So in this case,
we have this Background image.
So we use our Sprite Renderer
to actually see that image in our scene,
especially when you're making 2D games,
Sprite Renderers are
particularly useful.
Or if you have a character with items
or they're carrying something.
So with our Sprite Renderer,
on the right
there's an little property called
Sprite, and you can see currently
it's set to "Background_Town"
all the way
on the right side of the Inspector.
There's this little circle icon,
it's a radio button
so you can actually click on it.
And there are all these different
options.
So there's in fact actually 3 different
Backgrounds we can use.
So you can select one
that works for you best.
I kind of liked this forest scene.
It's very natural.
It's got a lot of bright colors
on it. So now I can just close out
of this window, and we have
a Background selected.
All right. So what you're going
to do is open up the Unity Hub,
and create a new
Prototype through Project.
Use the link below in the steps
to download the Project starter files.
Make sure to open
the Prototype 3 scene
and delete the sample scene.
And then you can select
the Background Object in the Hierarchy.
And then in the Sprite Renderer
Component, you can go to Sprite
and select a new Background image
to use if you want to use the city,
nature or town Background.
So now it's your turn.
[music]